You know does your
emergency room run soon.
Nixon coming to New Moon
dawned on you you really
become old the most through don't
think no stranger.
I have a very shy nice you
live where you would even
say on the range. You're so nice and calm.
They know.
Gine any reindeer get Christmas
with your nose so briars you
guys nice night tonight.
Then how the reindeer not been
shown the dogs with Rudolph
the Red nosed Reindeer you'll go down
and see it was the day before Christmas
and old through the hills the remainder
will play enjoying the spoons of skating
and coasting and flaming
the willows and hopscotch
and Leap Frog protected by Philip Bellows
who well you know
I read it a few times I write nothing.
I'm the guy off.
For Rudolph where most
reindeers noses are brownish
and tiny Rudolph was red very large
and quite telling me I
don't really know you know.
Come come.
LOU DOBBS TONIGHT you hang
up your stocking make
him live eat white rice
while away a way up north on this dark
funky night awaiting the time for his
Christmas Eve place.
Good old man this fog will
be hard to get through
the room is
required if I'm right
there is a dancer Prancer
next to Thomas to bed down a less a
better world.
To keep the direction.
Will I prefer a low income Americans.
Don't do it quick.
Oh you're married
now.
Good for your groceries.
I know
the air was still foggy and dark
and we're in the center of a
riot at the home of the deer.
But all this took time to
kill Santa with blue Miles.
Only he pulled toward the next
leap years from the dam plus
and burning the gloom came instead from
Rudolph's red nose at the head of the bed
and then came the greatest
idea in all this debate.
So Rudolph is told of the
dark and delay come into play
and losing the way I need you tonight
to leave all my dear on the rest of our
life to you and.
You want to help.
Don't worry come back for me
early on it's very dark you know
with those of the wonderful life old fans
of flu quickly the rest of the night
be a
good day a
plane went so fast
that before it was Dave the very
loved person was given the way he
gave you a room just a phone
Rudolph's mistake it's all
over tone
deaf ears who used to do
nothing but tease him.
Well no they do anything only to please.
Root out my boy and you know I'll run
but no greater I'll come come to a day
when riding with some guy
be my sway the number one.
Job number was I hope you'll get there
due to the post from grief I hereby
applying to compound the truth
and Rudolf just life from his head to his
toes until his pay for was as red as his
No Merry Christmas to zero in to
C.N.N. Now the rain came
and the shouting Andres grade
the red nosed main thing you go
down in here is.