And as happens these days when Trump makes
an appearance so do the protesters are
by when Scott has that story. This is where
all the action is taking place at the
Gaylord National Harbor that the president
speaks to his supporters but across the
street here of those who
don't support him they are
a group of protesters all
over the shuttle was
a relatively small but vocal group of
protesters gathered in the shadow of the
Gaylord National Harbor this morning
that it was a Their mission to send
a message to President Donald Trump and his
supporters Unfortunately his stance and
hers policy just don't match what the
people here need and what we want as
president you know we're supposed to have
the government serving the people and
right now that's not the case they targeted
all the usual suspects tribes pledged
to get rid of Obamacare and in
Prince George's County that's
a big deal not just because it's half
a million people that are going to health
care but when you combine that with the
fact that one of President Trump supporters
governor Hogan is trying to play games
with funding our new Prince George's
Hospital Center literally like access to
health care in our county is it is
literally on the line on the president's
immigration policy I don't think if you
represent the values certainly not of
Democrats and I don't think of conservatives
either and so I think this is
a really important moment and trumps promise
to make America great again trust and
believe the bill that may come back the
black cloak angle be to want to get new
jobs in these businesses he's bringing back
the coalition of groups spearheaded by
the Prince George's County Young Democrats
assembled directly across the street
from the sea packed gathering Trump
supporters passing by stopped to mingle with
protesters sparking moments
of debate and have
a vetting process now that the jury betting
is what you're doing that you can't
predict the extreme betting is what we have
now not surprisingly no points of view
appear to be altered but never played
here because you're coming from
a complete emotional standpoint I'm
coming from a logical standpoint. That's
a good likely are you right the building I
look at I do things I dare say we don't
have to fight and while some may think.
Viz guys are crazy they are not nor are
their opinions without conviction when
he was given regulations and bring Take
destroy the iris He just announced the
Emancipation Proclamation because anything
over ten percent taxes is legal slavery
I don't need no programs I just want my
money and asking you politely to stop
saying that I didn't ask and while the give
and take and times to appear tense it all
fell under the banner of democracy and
police say that's just fine this is exactly
what we wanted to see people able to
express their. Exercise
their freedom of speech. In
a place where right in front of the Gaylord
we didn't stick them blocks and blocks
away we wanted to make sure that they
felt like they were close enough to where
their voices could be heard I by eleven
twenty five Marine One was in the air
and the president was heading
back to Washington D.C.
The protests here lasted all of
a couple of hours the hope of course is
that the message resonates far longer but
that of course remains to be seen at
National Harbor Byron Scott C.T.V. News.