Soyuzmultfilm
Moscow
СAKE
written by V. Gorsky
directed by Petr Nossov
art directors Vladimir Arbekov, Igor Znamensky
music O. Gordeli
words (poems)
Ya. Akim, Lev Pozdneyev
cameramen Ye. Rizo, N. Klimova
sound Boris Filchikov
animators Victor Likhachev, M. Pershin,
Lidia Reztsova, Boris Zelensky, M. Kuprach,
Elizabeth Komova, Lev Pozdneyev, Elena Khludova
They sing:
-We dig our little bit of land,
and planting seeds
-Do not be lazy! It will grow!
By fall we'll eat pie's!
-Wheat will rise as high as a wall
-Do not be lazy! It will grow!
By fall we'll eat pie's!
All those day-old chicks make such a noise,
You can't get any sleep like that.
-I do not understand these chicks.
What are they doing?
-What? You're not strong enough!
-No way! It won't move!
-Okay, wait a minute! I will help!
laugh
-This is not easy, the stump has too many roots.
We need to call the neighbours for help.
-Sharik! Murzik!
-Could you give us a hand?
My health is not good.I have a stomach ache!
-I have bronchitis.
-I have swollen heels!
I'm shaking with fever!
coughs.
Toothache. Help!
-Oh! I cannot see with my right eye!
-All right, slackers, keep in bed!
We'll manage without you!
laugh.
-One, two, heave!
How frustrating this stump is!
-Sharik! Murzik! Come to work!
-That's really worrying.
-I am not accustomed to work.
- I am not a servant of chickens!
Chorus:-We support you and so
we get our share of the pie!
We'll  play nice songs for you!
Let's hear the balalaika!
laugh
-We have a sharp sickle,
Many bundles of wheat we'll cut.
-Do not be lazy! It will soon get done!
By fall we'll eat pie's!
Beat forcefully! Strike together in harmony!
-Do not be lazy! It will soon get done!
By fall we'll eat pie's!
Let's call-in their help, in any case.
-No use, it's a wasted effort!
Little chickens do not write me my lessons!
-Let her go. Perhaps they will come!
-Good day! I came to call you for your help
to thresh the corn.
We are just busy cleaning
We cleaned out the closet!
Help us, dear doggy! Help us pleas kitten!
The chickens are to small to manage this.
Hatchie!
-Gesundheit, auntie!
laugh
-Brother, your legs are too short!
-Do not talk, and help me!
-The time has come!
We reached the bottom of our porridge jar!
-We're out of crackers too!
-Murzik!, And Sharik!
-It has risen enough,
And now it's time to bake it!
-Where are you going?
-And where are you going?
-Just somewhere!-And I'm there first!
-Get out of the way,  cat!
Stand back!
-Give me that spoon!
-Who in the spring has worked in the field
gets his share!
-Lazy slackers
We didn't invite you for pie!
-Here, take it. I just gave up.
No, thank you. Take it yourself.
Bring back your spoon, and your empty bowl.
We do not feed lazy bums!